Guide to the Internation Brotherhood of Teamsters Graphic Communications Conference records, 1902-2006 IBT0006
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Public Information Department - William Moody Research files, 1902-2006; Series 1; 29.25 Linear Feet
  - Kirkland, Lane - Speech at John Dunlop's Retirement, 1985; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - ku Klux Klan, 1981; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - LaBaum, Edmund L., 1966; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Labor College of Canada, 1982; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Labor and Economic Crisis, 1975; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Labor Day, 1968-1970; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Labor Insitute of Public Affairs, 1983; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Labor Law, 1978,1982; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Labor Looks at Congress, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - Labor Looks at the 94th Congress, 1977 (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - Labor/Management Conference 1986 Report, Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Labor Party (UK) Interview of Neil Kinnock, 1985; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Labor PArty (US), 1975-1977; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Labor Press ILPA, 1973,1974,1978,1980; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Labor Today, 1976-1977; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America - Laborers Respond to Mother Jones, 1980; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Lan Drum - Griffin Law, 1966,1981; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Lansing 564M, 1984; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Leadership General, 1974,1984; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Leadership Seminar, 1965,1966,1968,1970,1973; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Leadership Training, 1967; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Left Wing, 1980; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Legislative Committee (GAIU), 1973; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Legislative Conferences - General, 1972; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Legislative and Political Conference, 1975; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Legislative and Political Conference May 3-5 1977, Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Lewis, John L., 1964; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Lie Detectors, 1986; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Lincoln, Abraham, 1968; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Linotype (The Typecase), 1976; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - LPIU - Awards For The Unionist, 1970; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - LPIU - Candidates For International Office, 1960,1965,1968,1969,1970-1972; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - LPIU Instuctor Development, 1968; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - LPIU Local Meeting Dates and Places, Undated; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - LPIU Membership Reports, 1966-1976; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - LPIU Membership Misc. Payments, merger program, retirement, pension, 1964; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - LPIU New HQ in Washington DC, 1971; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - LPIU News Letters and News Releases, 1965-1971; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Lithographers Union, 1961,1963,1969; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Lithographic Technical Foundation, 1960; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Lithography, 1965; Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Local Directory (GAIU), 1973; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Lockout - General Gravure Service, Hillside NJ, 1968; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Logos of GAIU,GCIU, 1974,1983; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Logotype, 1962,1964,1972,1977; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - London 517M, 1981-1986; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Los Angeles 63B, 1976; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Los Angeles Local 262, 1968,1983; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Los Angeles 404M, 1984-1986; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Louisville 552, 1981-1982; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Macarythy, Eugene, 1968; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Macellari, Eugene, 1965; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Marhsen - Local 507, 1978-1985; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Mailers Union - International General, 1971-1972; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Mailers Union - International Mailer, 1971,1972,1974; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Mailers Union - International Mailer, 1975,1976; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Mailers Union - International Mailer, 1977,1978; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Mailing to Canada, 1967,1983,1985; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Mailing Services - General, 1973-1974,1980; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Mailing Services Inc., 1965-1972; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Maurer, Fleisher, Zon, and Anderson, 1973-1975,1980; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Mcentee, Gerald, 1982; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - McFadden, William P, 1981,1983; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - McGovern, Goerge, 1971,1972; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - McNally, Michael P., 1985-1988; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - McKenzie, Murray, 1972-1980; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Meany, George, 1966-1980; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Members, 1970-1988; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Memo from Cope, 1977 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Meredith Burda Corporation, 1973,1974; Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Merger Trend in Unions, 1972; Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Merger - IPEU-ALA, 1961-1962; Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Merger - IPEU-ALA, 1963-1964; Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Merger - IPEU-ALA Photostatic Docs., 1941-1942; Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Merger - LPIU-ISEU, 1966; Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Merger - LPIU-IBB, 1970; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Merger - LPIU-IBB, 1971; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Merger - LPIU-IBB, 1971; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Merger - LPIU-IBB Merger Agreement, 1971-1972; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Merger - LPIU-IBB News Clippings, 1970-1972; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Merger - LPIU- Pressman Exploratory, 1966; Series 1 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Merger - GAIU-IPGCU, 1982-1983; Series 1 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Merger - GAIU-IPGCU WM's Meeting Notebooks, 1981-1982; Series 1 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Merger - GCIU-ITU IET interest, 1985; Series 1 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Medal Decorating, 1966-1973; Series 1 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Miami Local 78 Lithographer's Strike, 1961; Series 1 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Microfliming Services MCA and UMI, Xerox, 1975,1977-1985; Series 1 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Mid City Press, 1964-1969; Series 1 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Mid City Press, 1970-1980; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Midwestern State Conference Constitution (GAIU), 1979; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Milwakee - Local 277, 1984-1986; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Mine Workers of America (United), 1969-1982; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Minniapolis - SA Paul Local 229, 1981,1983; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Printed Matter and Newspaper Clippings, 1969-1986 (Box 66, Folder 35)
  - Mitchell, James H., 1987; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Mountpelier Local 745C, 1985; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Montreal 555, 1973,1980,1982-1984; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Moody, William - Resume, 1979; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Moody William - General A-M, 1965-1981; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Moody William- General N-Z, 1965-1985; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Morris, Joe - CLC, 1974; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Mount Morris - 91P, 1971,1980; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Multinationals, 1970,1972; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Murdock, Rupert (London Printers), 1986; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Nader, Ralph, 1975,1977,1980; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - National Accord Between Carter Administration and Organized Labor, 1979; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - National Association of Printers and Lithographers, 1967-1980; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - National Caucus of Labor Committees, 1975; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - National Committee to Abolish HUAC, 1968; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - National Footage League, 1977,1980; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - National Geographic (G+A-GRI), 1976; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - National Geographic Assn (UK) NGA, 1984; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - National Health and Security Act, 1970-1972; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - National Health and Security Act, 1973-1974; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - National Health and Security Act, 1975-1979,1981; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - National Health Insurance, 1971; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - National Health Insurance, 1971; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - National Labor Law Center - National Lawyers Guild, 1980; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - National Labor Relations Board, 1967-1978; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - National Urban Coalition, 1970-1978; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - National Urban Coalition Papers, 1970,1977; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - National Women's Political Caucus, 1981; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Natural Resources, 1981; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Nave Typographic Service, 1984; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Nazis (American), 1978; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Nelson, Gaylord (U.S. President Elections), 1974; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Nepotism (MJBJ) - Article From US News and World Report, 1978; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Nestle (Report on Third World Nutrition), 1982-1985; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Nuetrality Clauses, 1981; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - New Democratic Party, 1966,1971,1978,1979,1984; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Newengland Printer and Lithographer, 1967-1969; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - New Republic - WM, Letter To The Editor, 1972; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - New Right, 1981; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Newsletter Clinic GAIU 1978 Convention, Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Newsletter Clinic, 1975; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Newsletter Clinic- Toronto Convention, 1968,1974,1975; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Newsletter Clinic - Toronto Convention, 1968,1975,1982; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Local News Letters, 1970,1973,1974,1977,1980,1983; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper History, 1985; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Niles Local 158B, 1980-1982; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper Design Notebook, 1979; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper Guild, American, 1965-1967,1969,1970,1972-1976,1979,1981,1983; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper Guild, American, 1973-1984; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - New York I-P School, 1968,1982; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - New York 119B-43B, 1971,1981,1983,1985; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - New York 51M, 1984-1986; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - New York - ALA Local (SWAYDUCK), 1968-1971,1974-1975,1981; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - New York - ALA Local (SWAYDUCK), 1964,1969,1970; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - New York - ALA Notes On Local 1 Meeting, 1963 September 24; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - New York State Official Directory of Union Made Products and Services, 1967-1973 (Box 66, Folder 19)
  - Newspapers, Joint Operations, and the Antitrust Laws: What It's All About (Box 66, Folder 18)
  - Nigeria WFTU-NLC, 1982; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Nixon, Richard M., 1971,1973; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Noll, 1985,1987,1988; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - 28th Annual North America Newspaper Conference, 1984,1985; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - North American Precis Syndicate, 1982; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Northwest Conference, 1976; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Norton, James (Correspondence, Clippings, Newsletter), 1985-1987; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Norwitz, 1976,1979,1981,1983,1984,1986,1988,1989,1991; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - NOW - National Orginization for Women, 1978,1982,1983; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Nuclear Disarmament/Energy, 1979-1981,1983,1985; Series 1 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Occupational Lithography, 1985; Series 1 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Occupational Safety and Health Act (OSHA), 1972-1974; Series 1 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - OKI - 508M, 1982-1984; Series 1 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - O'Neill, James, 1962-1964,1966; Series 1 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - O'Sullivan, Daniel E. - Union Labor Life Insurance - ULLICO, 1984; Series 1 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Organizing - General, 1960-1980; Series 1 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Organizing - General, 1966,1969,1972,1974,1979,1982; Series 1 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Organizing - Clippings, 1977,1980,1981; Series 1 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Organizing Meeting - First GAIU 1972, 1966,1969,1971,1972; Series 1 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Organizing Meeting - AFL - Food and Beverage Trade Dept. Materials, 1970-1990; Series 1 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - OSHA - OccupationalSafety and Health, 1970,1972,1976,1981; Series 1 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Oral History In U.S., 1966; Series 1 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Overseas Trip, 1979-1980; Series 1 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Overseas Trip, 1980; Series 1 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Ottawa 191B - Testimonial to Maybel Lynch, 1967; Series 1 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Pacific Northwest 767M, 1985,1986; Series 1 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Pacific Region Conference (GAIU), 1975-1988; Series 1 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Paper, 1982,1983,1985; Series 1 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - (United)Paperworkers International Union, 1966,1974,1978; Series 1 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Paquette, Leonard R., 1979-1981; Series 1 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - PATCO, 1981; Series 1 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Pattern Makers Journal, 1987; Series 1 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Payboard Regulations, 1971-1972; Series 1 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Pay Out of Union Leaders, 1980; Series 1 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Pennsylvania AFL-CIO, 1974,1975; Series 1 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Pension Communicator, 1975; Series 1 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Pension Law, 1974; Series 1 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Pension Reform Act, 1975-1976; Series 1 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Pension Plam GAIVA DA, 1976; Series 1 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Pension Plans - Graphic Industry Joint Pension Trust, 1976; Series 1 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Pension Merger - bookbinders and Graphic Arts Industry, undated; Series 1 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Pensions/Retirement - General, 1967,1969,1971,1972,1976; Series 1 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Per Capita Fees - History of, 1977; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Per Capita Tax Freeze - Resolution, 1986; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Plate Makers Educational Research Institute, 1964,1966,1971,1977; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Peters, Abe - Local 555, 1964,1965,1973; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Peterson, Ether biography, 1965; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Philadelphia Lithographic Institute, 1964-1967,1972; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Philadelphia 2B, 1981; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Philadelphia Local 7P, 1979,1980; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Philadelphia 14L, 1969,1979,1989; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Philadelphia Organizing Drive At Curtis Publishing Co. - 14L LPIU, 1966-1967; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Philadelphia Plan, 1972; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Phoenix 512, 1983-1984; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Photoengravers - The American Photoengraver, 1961-1963; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Photoengravers Fiftey Years of Progress, 1950; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Photoengravers - Pension Plan Financial Reports merged, 1966-1981; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Photographic (Services), 1966,1968,1969,1971,1973,1974,1978,1984; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - photographs - Stocks, 1979,1981,1986,1987; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Photopolymer Relief Printing Plates, 1977; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Pittsburgh 24-6, 1972,1983; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Plant Closings, 1975,1978; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Plant Guard Workers of America, 1970; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Pleasure, Robert J. (biography), 1985; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Poland, Undated; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Political Action (Elections 1966,1968), 1966,1968-1970; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Polling (Union Publications Survey), 1981; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Pooling Fund, 1973,1978; Series 1 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Pollution, 1969-1971,1973; Series 1 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Postal Rates, 1973,1978,1985-1986; Series 1 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Postal Rates, 1974,1976,19780,1984,1986,1988; Series 1 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Postal Regulations, 1964-1976,1979,1984; Series 1 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Postal Regulation, 1978-1982; Series 1 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Postal Regulation, 1976-1978,1982; Series 1 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Postal Regulation, 1990,1992-1994,1997,2000-2002,2006; Series 1 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Postal Requirnments Statement of Ownership, 1964-1967,1970,1972,1977,1979,1985,1986; Series 1 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Postal Service Manual, 1977; Series 1 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Presidents US - On Organized Labor, 1966; Series 1 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Press Atlantic Labor Conference, 1965-1973; Series 1 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - PAI - Press Associates Inc, 1962,1965,1970,1983; Series 1 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Press Contacts, 1965,1966,1970; Series 1 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Press Relations Wire (Services), 1970,1982; Series 1 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Press Release - LPIU - GAIU, 1965-1979; Series 1 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Print '74 TDCE - Technical Development Educational Committee, 1974; Series 1 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Printing, 1985; Series 1 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Printing and Graphic Communications Union, 1960,1965,1966,1970,1974; Series 1 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - PDI - Printing Development Inc, 1967-1968,1971; Series 1 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Printing Editors' Conference, 1965; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - PIA - Printing Industries of America, 1962-1981; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - PIA - Printing Industries of America Inc Newsletter and Releases, 1972-1973; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - PIA - LPIU Roundtable, 1968,1972,1973; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Printing/News Merger ALA-LPIU Local 1 - NY Withdraw, 1966; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Priting Pressmen Financial Report, 1963-1964,1980; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Printing Pressmen Convention Committee Appointments, 1928-1970; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Printing Week, 1966,1967,1972; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Profits in Graphic Arts, 1976; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Pennsylvania State University Archives Correspondence, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 20)
  - PEP - Project In Equal Progression (Program by GAIU), 1976,1980; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Progressive Alliance, 1980; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Providence Locals 239M 39P, 1980,1981,1984,1986; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Publicationd Contract Committee, 1980; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Publci Ownership, 1983; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Public Printer, 1965,1973,1981,1982; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Public Relations, 1969,1971,1972,1975-1979,1982; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Publicity Club of new York "clippings", 1965-1967; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Pulp and Paper Industry (non-profit associat), 1967; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers - Merger, 1965,1967; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Quality of Work life - American Center for The Quality of Life, 1979; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Quebec - Canada Re-Election Liberal Government, 1973; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Quebec 509M, 1981,1983,1984,1987; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Quebec Labor Code, 1978; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Quirk, William F., 1974; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Railroads - Railway, 1968,1978; Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Randolph, a. Philip APRI - A Phillip Randolph Institute, 1979; Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Reagan, Ronald Economic Policy - Clipping, 1982,1983; Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Realities of Metrication Report, 1977 (Box 66, Folder 26)
  - Referendum Ballot 1965 - Ammendments to the constitution LPIU, 1965,1967; Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Referendum Committee, 1979; Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Referendum on Organizing 1980, 1978,1980; Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Regional Conferences Book Binders, 1973; Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Reeves Bros, Inc, 1966-1968; Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Remmel, Peter J., 1975; Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Representatives and Organizers (formation of union), 1967,1979,1984; Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Republic Coroporation Annual Report, 1969; Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Retirement (At 65), 1971,1974,1977,1980; Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Retirement Conference - Pre-Retirment Meeting, 1970,1974,1978,1981; Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Reuther, Walter P. (AFL-CIO-Differences), 1966,1967,1970; Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Right To Work, 1960-1990; Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Ring-GAIU, 1977; Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Risdon, Walter F. Scholorship Fund, 1965-1972; Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Roberts, Lillian, 1981; Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Robots, 1981; Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Rochester Polychrome - 230, 1981; Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Rochester Institute of Technology, 1966-1967; Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Rogers, Ray, 1985; Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Rohan, Alexander J., 1986; Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D. - memorial postage stamp, 1982; Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - RotoGravure Conference 1967, Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - RotoGravure Conference 1968 + 1969, Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - RotoGravure Conference 1970, 1969,1970; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - RotoGravure Conference 1973, Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - RotoGravure Conference 1974, Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - RotoGravure Bargaining, 1973; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - RotoGravure General, 1976-1979; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Rountable Lithographers, 1963; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Russia, 1978-1979; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Russia Grain Deal, 1975; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Ruttenberg, Stanley H., 1965; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Sacremento Local 35B, 1981; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Safety and Health - General, 1971-1976; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Safety and Health - Guides, 1971-1976; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Safety On The Job, 1971-1973; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Salaries of Union Leaders, Buisiness Executives, 1978-1986; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Salem Il Local 787C, 1986; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - SALT II Treaty, 1979; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Safrancisco Local 3 B, 1982-1984; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Safrancisco Local 17, 1962-1967; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Safrancisco Local 280, 1970-1984; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Safrancisco Local 583M, 1986; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Santa, John f., 1961; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Sawyer, donald L. GPO, 1983,1984; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Scab - Jack London definition, 1972-1979; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Scanner Survey, 1974; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Schaffer, Kenneth A, 1962-1967; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Scharff, Monroe B, 1961; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Schlesinger, Carl, 1982; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Schmidt, Edward, 1984 January 6; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Scholorship Programs LPIU and PDI, GCIU, 1976,1985; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Schroeder, William H, 1966-1973,1975-1977,1979; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Scranton 97B, 1983; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Seafares International Union, 1965-1970; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Seattle Local 39C - also Local 747 Seatle/portland, 1983,1985; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Seeger, Pete, 1986; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Seldes, George, 1985; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - Seminars - Educational LPIU, 1965-1966; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - Seminar - Educational LPIU, 1968; Series 1 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Seminar - Educational, 1970-1971; Series 1 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Seminar - Leadership GAIU, 1973; Series 1 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Seminar - Training, 1973,1979; Series 1 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Senatobia Local 532, 1976-1982; Series 1 (Box 49, Folder 5)